{
    "crosswordNumber": 3,
    "horizontalEntries": [
        {
            "StartX": 0,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A game played with a bat and ball",
                "answer": "BASEBALL"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 1,
            "StartY": 8,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "The largest continent on Earth",
                "answer": "ASIA"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 5,
            "StartY": 9,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A red gemstone often used in jewelry",
                "answer": "RUBY"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 0,
            "StartY": 10,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "The main ingredient in bread",
                "answer": "FLOUR"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 5,
            "StartY": 11,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A fruit that is often made into raisins",
                "answer": "GRAPE"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 6,
            "StartY": 2,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "Honey loving animal",
                "answer": "BEAR"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 6,
            "StartY": 5,
            "isHorizontal": true,
            "entry": {
                "question": "Source or origin of something ",
                "answer": "ROOT"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        }
    ],
    "verticalEntries": [
        {
            "StartX": 0,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "An animal known for building dams",
                "answer": "BEAVER"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 2,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A place where you go to learn",
                "answer": "SCHOOL"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 4,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A round object used in many sports",
                "answer": "BALL"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 4,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A professional dancer",
                "answer": "BALLERINA"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 6,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A place where you can borrow books",
                "answer": "LIBRARY"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 9,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A holiday celebrated on December 25th",
                "answer": "CHRISTMAS"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 11,
            "StartY": 0,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A flying vehicle with wings",
                "answer": "AIRPLANE"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 1,
            "StartY": 6,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "The opposite of 'big'",
                "answer": "SMALL"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 7,
            "StartY": 7,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "An animal known for its stripes",
                "answer": "ZEBRA"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        },
        {
            "StartX": 11,
            "StartY": 9,
            "isHorizontal": false,
            "entry": {
                "question": "A vehicle used to carry passengers",
                "answer": "BUS"
            },
            "IsEntryFilled": false
        }
    ]
}